O Stree come tomorrow
Prakash .
Prakash !
STREE
O Stree come tomorrow
♪ " The heart 's completely open , ♪ ♪ with no hook or button ... " ♪
♪ " No button . " ♪
♪ " Dreams are larger than life ... " ♪
♪ " ... and a mind that cares for no one . " ♪
♪ " ... cares for no one . " ♪
♪ " My dreams are too ♪ ♪ big to fit in this city . " ♪
♪ " Bigger than the city ... " ♪
♪ " I can fix your pain ♪ ♪ with just a smile . " ♪
♪ " I am the tailor of Heart . " ♪
♪ " Like a bird soaring in the skies . " ♪
♪ Hey ... ♪
♪ " I am the tailor of love . " ♪
♪ " Like a bird soaring in the skies . " ♪
♪ " I am the tailor of Heart . " ♪
♪ " Stitch me a beautiful dress , ♪ ♪ sweetheart ... " ♪
♪ " ... which makes me ♪ ♪ look more charming . " ♪
♪ " I am the tailor of Heart . " ♪
♪ " Like a bird soaring in the skies . " ♪
Uncle ... you start this charade in every festival , don 't you ?
Vicky , there 's still time .
But , this is no ordinary ink .
These are crushed bones of a bat mixed with the pee of a white crow .
That 's how this ink is prepared .
Uncle , sell these stories to those who like reading Aesop 's fables .
We 're the modern generation .
The entire city believes in this ignorance .
Vicky , any house that has this ink outside their house
will always be safe from ' Stree ' .
I see ...
Have you ever heard that the Ambani 's daughter was possessed ?
Or the Tatas or Birla 's were haunted .
I know she will come .
Loosen your pockets and let me finish writing .
Uncle , don 't forget to write on our wall too .
And listen , write it in bold .
Otherwise , she might not read it and come right in .
Yes , I will .
Your mouth will end up like that aunty .
Close the gate , mister .
Or the cow will barge in .
I am the watchman as well .
So you finally found time to come home .
What 's the matter ?
- You should also come with me from tomorrow . - I don 't need to .
The sewing machine gives me all the exercise I need .
And , you don 't need this either .
Or soon you 'll be hanging from a hanger .
Was that a joke ?
And you 're trying to be wise .
I 'm already observing a fast for the next four days .
And , you 're making me waste my energy .
- Another fast ? - Focus on your job .
Soon the ladies will queue up .
I 've told you before stop taking alteration work .
" Loosen the petticoat , tighten my blouse . "
We 'll only accept orders for stitching new clothes .
Brand new clothes only .
Only ?
And what will you do for the rest of the year , son ?
Ring the bell .
Daddy , explaining you is impossible .
Listen ...
Listen ... Listen ... Listen ...
You should spend some time learning how to run the shop .
Otherwise , if someday your dad passes away
you won 't be able to run the show alone .
Even if Death comes himself to collect your soul , you won 't die .
Even when your fingers will become frail , you 'll still be altering lady 's dresses .
Son , soon you 'll be following in my footsteps .
Daddy , I wasn 't born to alter lady 's dresses .
Then what are you destined for , son ?
I don 't know yet , dad . But I will know pretty soon .
♪ ( Rap Song ) ♪
Let them in .
How are you , brother Vicky ?
Stitch a dress for me .
Take down sister-in-law 's measurements .
Step back a little .
Length ; 48 , Shoulder ; 14.5 .
- Take off the shawl , sister-in-law . - Yes .
Arm-hole ; 16 , Wrist ; 7 , Chest ; 38 , waist ; 42 .
Turn around , sister-in-law .
Hip ; 44 , Neck : 10
Deep or Medium ?
No , not deep .
Keep it medium .
Deep 's better , sister-in-law . It 's in fashion these days .
You 'll look nice .
I am telling you , my son is the tailor-incarnation of God .
Do you want it tighter ?
The shoulder on this dress ...
But this idiot doesn 't respect his own talent .
( Rap Song )
What is this boy , Khan sir ? What is he ?
I 've stitched thousands of clothes .
But the way his fingers moves on the machine
feels like God 's fingers moving on the machine .
The way he handles the scissors sounds like Goddess Saraswati 's playing her Veena .
When he puts a thread in the needle , I can hear conches resonating in my ears .
I am sure it 's some connection from his past life .
♪ " I am the tailor of Heart . " ♪
♪ " Like a bird soaring in the skies . " ♪
I 'll be back in 10 minutes , dad .
Break time .
♪ " I am the tailor of Heart . " ♪
Hi .
- Is your name Vicky ? - Yes .
I saw you last year at the festival .
Okay ...
I 've heard a lot about you .
I don 't live here , but I come every year during the festival .
I see ... okay .
- Can you stitch a dress for me ? - Okay .
- How long ? - 2 weeks .
Can 't you do it earlier ?
How about 10 days ?
I want it on the last day of the festival .
To wear it during the auspicious veneration .
Vicky , please .
Give it earlier .
It 's okay .
I 'll get it done by someone else .
Thank you .
Two days ... Two ...
- Two days . - Thank you so much .
My measurements .
Take off the jacket .
Turn around .
Turn .
Again .
Done .
Ohh ...
Thank you .
I 'll be visiting the temple in the evening .
Good .
For the evening veneration .
Very good .
Visiting the temple ...
Okay .
( Religious venerations )
One .
Saw ?
She doesn 't even look at you , and you can already hear wedding bells .
And you 're Mister know-it-all , aren 't you ?
Whenever I pass through her lane , she always looks at me .
No , she doesn 't , she stares at you .
Are you all right ?
Will you say something ? What happened ?
- Love at first eye-sight . - First eye-sight .
Love at first sight .
We both attended the English Speaking course together .
Don 't try to be Shakespeare .
Who is the girl ?
The same girl who attended the festival last year .
The one with brown eyes .
- One with the long hair . - Yeah ...
The one you bragged about last year ?
I wasn 't bragging .
She came out of nowhere like a cool breeze .
Took my hand and said ...
" Vicky , please ! "
She held your hand .
Ba * * *
- And she even said please ? - Yes .
He is lying and you believe him .
Swear on my sewing machine .
She held your hand and said , Vicky , please .
" Vicky , please ! "
Vicky , please !
That 's what I am saying , Vicky , please .
You have no emotions at all .
Give me your hand .
" Vicky , please ! "
Now that 's emotion .
But why you ?
She wants me to stitch a dress .
Stitch a dress .
I have a readymade dress shop .
Who gets dresses stitched nowadays .
You idiot , stitched dresses have a different charisma .
And love is never readymade .
It 's always tailor-made .
Right .
" Vicky , please ! "
Bro put it on my tab .
Jealous .
She held this hand .
Smell it .
Sunflower .
I think you should start planning your wedding .
Even I can hear wedding bells , Jana .
Hey , ... snap out of your dream world .
Today is the first day of the festival .
Lokesh is throwing a party at his uncle 's home .
So we 're going to have a ball for the next four nights .
Nobody be late .
Meaning party all night and , in the morning ...
Full tight .
Right .
But that 's in the morning .
♪ " Just tell me why ♪ ♪ do you throw tantrums . " ♪
♪ " I can follow you around ♪ ♪ like your crazy lover . " ♪
♪ " I feel a little shy to convey . " ♪
♪ " But , I want to sleep in your arms . " ♪
♪ " I 've been telling ♪ ♪ you since February came . " ♪
♪ " Darling , ♪ ♪ step out of Chanderi for me . " ♪
♪ " Come over to my mansion . " ♪
You guys go ahead , I 'll join you later .
What are you planning to do out here ?
My heart 's a little restless .
I guess I 'll just sit here and pray .
What 's wrong with you , Vicky ? Why are you feeling so religious today ?
That dancer from Bhopal must have arrived too .
I 've been waiting for a year to see her .
- Let 's go ... - Jana , you just go .
- I 'll come later ... - Hold on .
He 's going to see that girl .
One who said " Vicky Please " .
And he 's making excuses to us .
Is sister-in-law coming ?
Then we 'll wait too .
- What ? - No one 's coming .
- I 'll get the offerings for you . - What offerings .
Stop making excuses , Vicky .
Remember , females have been the reason for the downfall of men .
What ?
It was a female who disrupted Vishwamitra 's penance .
And I am not Vishwamitra .
And I am not looking for a boon .
I am not standing on one leg and waiting for some Meneka to disrupt my penance .
What do you think ?
You explain to him .
He 's talking nonsense .
Take him with you , Jana .
This is not about any girl .
Let 's go , Bittu .
Go on .
Come soon .
You too . - Come on .
I 'm coming .
Not you too .
Jana .
Go on .
Why did you say yes ?
Hi .
Hello .
I thought you didn 't understand .
No , I understood , but it takes me a little time to ...
I mean I 've very little experience in ...
I ... I ...
- Do you have a problem in speaking ? - No . Why ?
Because if you do , it can be treated .
No , no , I can speak pretty well .
Peacock .
Peacock is our National bird .
Peacock has a long and sharp beak .
The Peacock is around 1.5 feet tall .
The Peacock is a beautiful bird .
The Peacock 's feather has many colors .
Some people believe when the female peacock drinks the male peacock 's tear
then a baby peacock is born .
When the Peacock dances during the monsoons
people are enchanted to see the sight .
Just like I was enchanted when I saw you ...
Sorry .
By the way , you 're looking really nice tonight .
Even you 're looking ... alright .
Thank you .
- You 're late . The veneration is over . - Is it ?
Yes .
I didn 't realize I was late .
It 's the ambiance .
But I will inform you before the veneration starts tomorrow .
I will call you .
Store your number on this .
I don 't carry a mobile .
You don 't .
Okay .
So if I ... or anyone else wants to talk to you , or call you
then how to do that ?
I don 't know about others , but
if you want to talk , then ...
Then ?
Just think about me . And I 'll come over .
Fine , I will do that .
Letter .
" To Vicky . "
For me ?
No .
Read it tomorrow morning , after you 've freshened up .
After ...
Okay .
Thank you .
By the way , it 's quite late , isn 't it ?
It 's dark everywhere .
I wait for this darkness .
Okay ...
FIRST NIGHT
What 's the point of owning a bike if you can 't afford fuel ?
Do you have a problem with petrol ?
It 's always getting over .
Forget the petrol .
Think about Vicky .
Stop fighting , Bittu .
It was his good luck , that he found a girl .
But he could 've introduced us as well .
Why isn 't he introducing us to her ?
I think there is no girl in the first place .
And if there is one , then there 's something wrong with her .
What was that sound ?
What sound ? I 've been speaking all this time ?
What sound did you hear ?
There , I heard it again .
What ?
- Brother Rudra . - Hello .
Hello , brother Rudra .
- Are you two in your right mind ? - Yes , we are .
- Where are you two going at this hour ? - Why ?
What happened ?
The festival has begun .
She will be out hunting for the next four days .
Who ?
She .
Stree .
Stop scaring him , brother Rudra .
I am not scaring him , just warning you .
Look , our city is the only place in this world
where no male steps out alone during these days of the festival .
She abducts male , leaving only his clothes behind .
Only his clothes .
It 's just that I like you two , you two are like family
that 's why I was telling you , otherwise ...
Brother Rudra , please tell us .
Form a triangle . Form a triangle .
Come here .
What is that ?
Beer .
All right . I have mine .
Yes .
There are certain rules to escape the wrath of Stree .
Rule no . 1 .
Under no circumstances , and I mean none ... don 't step out of the house alone .
And only those men are safe , who have written outside their home , O Stree ...
Rule no . 2 .
If in case you 've to step out , then don 't try to be a lion , be a wolf instead .
- Wolf ? - Why ?
- Travel in packs , not alone . - I see .
Rule no . 3 .
If you ever come across the Stree
then she will first call out your name .
Hello , Tom-Dick-Harry .
What do you do ?
Take off your slippers , hold it in your hand , and ...
- Run ! - No !
No running .
Keep walking .
Do what ?
Then she will call out to you again .
This time with more passion .
And what do you do ?
Keep walking .
Then she will call out to you again , for the third time .
With an enchanting , alluring voice .
Like an angel .
" Embrace me now ... because this night may not come again . "
That 's the kind of emotions you 'll feel .
Your breathing will get faster , your heart will start pounding .
Bedroom . Bedroom . Bedroom will be the only thing on your mind .
And what do you do ?
- Keep walking . - No .
No man could ever resist the Stree when she calls out for the third time .
You will start losing control over yourself .
And as soon as you turn around ...
Gone !
But brother Rudra , there must be some way .
Yes .
Rule no . 4 .
And the most important thing to remember if you want to escape the Stree .
At any point ...
Yes , Shama .
What ?
You 're coming into my life .
I am coming right over .
Brother Rudra .
You didn 't finish the 4th rule .
Keep walking ! Keep walking ! Keep walking !
Don 't make a noise .
- Wait a minute . - No !
Keep walking ! Keep walking !
Bittu .
Jana , look .
What ?
Someone 's out there .
Bittu . Wait .
Stop .
Bittu .
Stop Bittu , for your mother 's sake .
- Why are you running ? - Because you 're running .
Come on . - Come .
What was that ? - I haven 't the slightest clue .
Don 't tell Vicky anything . or he 'll make fun of us .
Do you understand or not ?
Do you understand ?
Where were you two ?
What happened ?
- Huh ! - Nothing .
What ...
♪ " Oh , my silly beloved ... " ♪
♪ " ... snap out of your illusion . " ♪
♪ " Stop being afraid . " ♪
♪ " Stop making gestures ♪ ♪ from a distance . " ♪
♪ " Open the door to ♪ ♪ your heart wide apart ... " ♪
♪ " ... and say it out loud . " ♪
♪ " Don 't be scared . " ♪
♪ " Tell me what 's your ♪ ♪ plan for tonight . " ♪
♪ " I want to be struck by lightning . " ♪
♪ " Start a fire in my heart . " ♪
♪ " If you come with us , baby and ... " ♪
♪ " Shake your hips ... " ♪
♪ " Shake it ... Shake it ... " ♪
♪ " Cross your eyes ... with us . " ♪
♪ " Cross your eyes ... " ♪
♪ " Shake your hips ... " ♪
♪ " Shake it ... Shake it ... " ♪
♪ " Cross your eyes ... " ♪
♪ " Cross your eyes ... with us . " ♪
♪ " Take my heart , sweetheart ... " ♪
♪ " Take my life ... " ♪
♪ " But just ... " ♪
♪ " Just ... shake your hips for me . " ♪
♪ " Take my heart , sweetheart ... " ♪
♪ " Take my life ... " ♪
♪ " But just ... " ♪
♪ " Just ... shake your hips for me . " ♪
♪ " Shake it ... Shake it ... " ♪
♪ " Cross your eyes ... " ♪
♪ " Cross your eyes ... with us . " ♪
♪ " These beautiful sights ... " ♪
♪ " The stars in the sky ... " ♪
♪ " ... the season of spring ♪ ♪ that 's arrived ... " ♪
♪ " ... its all for you my love . " ♪
♪ " My love ... " ♪
♪ " ... and my joys ... " ♪
♪ " Take anything you want , sweetheart . " ♪
♪ " These beautiful sights ... " ♪
♪ " The stars in the sky ... " ♪
♪ " ... the season of spring ♪ ♪ that 's arrived ... " ♪
♪ " ... is all for you my love . " ♪
♪ " My love ... " ♪
♪ " ... and my joys ... " ♪
♪ " Take anything you want , sweetheart . " ♪
♪ " I want to be struck by lightning . " ♪
♪ " Start a fire in my heart . " ♪
♪ " If you come with us , baby and ... " ♪
♪ " Shake your hips ... " ♪
♪ " Shake it ... Shake it ... " ♪
♪ " Cross your eyes ... " ♪
♪ " Cross your eyes ... with us . " ♪
♪ " Shake your hips ... " ♪
♪ " Shake it ... Shake it ... " ♪
♪ " Cross your eyes ... with us . " ♪
♪ " Shake your hips ... " ♪
♪ " Shake it ... Shake it ... " ♪
♪ " Cross your eyes ... with us . " ♪
Bye .
♪ " Shake your hips ... " ♪
♪ " Shake it ... Shake it ... " ♪
O Stree come tomorrow
♪ " Cross your eyes ... with us . " ♪
♪ " Shake it ... Shake it ... " ♪
Go on .
Go .
Come on . Come in .
She 's my girlfriend .
I called her over for ' friendship ' !
Come in .
This kind of ' Friendship ' isn 't allowed in here .
Wasn 't it enough that we called a dancer ?
Uncle will never approve of this .
Just go out and start the generator , okay .
Why didn 't you inform me before that there are going to be more people ?
Don 't worry , darling .
I 've already reserved a room for us upstairs .
No one 's going to disturb us .
Just you and me . Me and you .
All alone in a room .
Well , if I had known , I would 've brought my friends along too .
And even your friends could 've snuggled up with them in a room .
Naughty .
Go upstairs .
Narender . Narender . Narender
♪ " Shake it ... Shake it ... " ♪
Come on .
- Are you carrying protection ? - Protection ?
No protection , no friendship .
Oh ... protection .
♪ " Shake it ... Shake it ... " ♪
Hello . Who is it ?
Jana . Are you carrying protection ?
Protection .
No , I don 't carry one .
Let 's ask one of the guys .
Guys ... is anyone carrying protection ?
Come on , quickly .
Hurry up .
Lights back . Lights back . Lights back .
I got the stuff .
Why have you turned off the lights ?
I like the lights on . Because now I 've protection .
This thing is older than my grandfather .
Such a cheap quality .
Yes .
Narender .
- What happened ? - There ...
What ?
Outside the window .
Someone dragged him out of the window .
Narender .
I came into the room and someone dragged him outside .
Stay here .
You go check .
Narender .
Clothes .
Clothes ?
Narender 's clothes .
Only his clothes .
Stree took him .
This is Stree 's doing .
Whenever she takes any man with her , she leaves his clothes behind .
But I don 't understand one thing ? How did Stree come inside ?
I don 't know .
I wrote " O Stree come tomorrow " on the wall
so that we can party peacefully .
Someone erased it .
I think that someone intentionally erased it .
Who peed on the wall ?
Who was it ?
Speak up now .
- Vicky ? - You did it .
No , it wasn 't me .
Oh really ? Then who did this ?
Right ... you went out in the middle of the dance .
You peed on the wall .
Yes , I did .
It didn 't say no peeing here .
Get lost .
Why did you have to pee there of all the places ?
My pee , my will , I can pee anywhere I want .
We lost a friend because of you .
He 's a junkie .
He must be high and wandering around .
We won 't hear anything against our friend .
- You made him disappear . - I didn 't do anything .
You made him disappear . You peed on the wall .
Just a second .
Stop ! Stop ! Stop , guys ! Stop !
What 's the point of beating up Jana ?
Your friend 's missing , go look for him .
Stop ranting Stree .
It 's pretty late .
Daddy must be waiting for me .
Even I didn 't tell my mom that I 'm coming here .
Fine , let 's come back tomorrow .
Letter .
Here 's the letter .
Brother , some madam 's here to see you .
Who is it ?
Tell her to come back later .
It 's her .
Take a look for yourself .
What the ...
- Did you tell her that I am at home ? - I did , brother ?
Come here .
What are you doing here ?
- I want my money . - What money ?
Money for the ' friendship ' .
Your friend didn 't pay me for the ' friendship ' .
So ?
So you 're going to pay me .
Why will I pay ?
I see ... you pee on the wall and I won 't get my money .
Has the government put a ban on my pee ?
I can pee anywhere I want .
Pay up quietly .
I heard that the friendship never happen .
We were halfway through ...
Please sister , I don 't have that kind of money .
I don 't have money ...
Look here , stop making excuses
otherwise , I will come down here with my friends and make a scene .
Calm down .
And , your father won 't like it .
I have heard a lot about him .
How much do I pay , sister ?
She 's collecting donation .
I think 3000 will be fine .
Take some lessons from him .
Jai Mata Di .
So mister , are you going to stand around like this or put something on .
Take care of your son .
He 's bustling with energy .
Son , I 'm going to share a really important experience of life .
Youth ... is a weird phase .
The body bustles with vitality .
A tank full of energy .
And this energy ... craves to come out .
But this body ... is puzzled about what to do or not to do .
And this restlessness
provokes it to have friendship with the opposite sex .
Dad , I hope you know what friendship means here .
Friendship .
Son , I was born in this town before you .
I 've had a lot of friendship back in my days .
- You had friendships . - I did .
Yes , but once I met your mother
she completely changed my point of view .
The union of a male and a female ...
- Listen to me . - Go on .
The union of a male and a female is pure .
It 's auspicious .
Like the union of Heaven and Earth .
The confluence of Shiv and Shakti .
But why are you telling me all this ?
I telling you so that you don 't pay for friendship .
When did I pay for friendship ?
- And what about her ... - Dad , she wasn 't here for me .
I didn 't pay for friendship .
Listen to me first .
My advice to you is that you must wait for a companion
with whom you can enjoy this process for the rest of your life .
And learn to control this energy bustling in your body till then .
And if you can 't , then ...
Then what ?
Then be self-reliant .
Cater to your needs .
Meaning ...
Meaning ... yourself .
How , daddy ?
I mean ...
Loss of words ?
Come on . Go out .
Listen ...
Energy .
Where is my energy ?
My dear Vicky .
If she 's started with ' my dear ' then she will end it with ' with love ' .
Okay .
My dear Vicky , how are you ?
What a stupid question ?
She just met yesterday and today she wants to know how you are .
Keep reading .
Honestly speaking I was really happy to meet you .
After talking to you I felt like that we 've known each other for a long time .
Since I retreated ...
Returned .
Sorry , since I returned after meeting you
I want to meet you again .
And this time when we meet , my dear Vicky
can you bring these things for me ?
PTO .
A quarter brandy .
Half a kilo of mutton .
A kilo of charred glass .
Thornapple flower .
Hair of a cat .
- And ... - And ?
The tail of a lizard !
Thanking you , with love .
With love . See ...
What is this stupid stuff ?
Who asks to get stuff like these ?
Plus she drinks .
So what if she drinks ?
Sister-in-law is cool .
That 's not the point .
She wants you to get the tail of a lizard .
And you 're a tailor , not the ancestor of lizards .
You 're prepared to go on this impossible mission because she told you .
Jana has been telling to you to stitch a shirt for him .
But did you ?
I have been telling you to let 's go to Goa .
Trying to be a hero for the girl .
You say something .
What now ?
- She 's asked so politely ... - So ?
Then I must get it .
What ?
It 's very simple .
Guys always do what girls tell them to .
That 's it .
Shahjahan built the Taj Mahal for his love .
And our brother chasing cats and lizards .
Whoever imagined love would fall to such levels in 500 years .
Tell me something , don 't you think something is wrong ?
Right and wrong is just a point of view , Bittu .
Don 't try to be wise .
I am telling you , I have a bad feeling about this .
Something is wrong about this girl ?
Got it . Got it . Got it .
Got it .
Come on , now hurry up .
That Stree already took one male last night .
We must return home before she comes out to hunt .
I am going as fast as I can .
Don 't be scared . I am with you .
You can 't handle one woman , and now you 're scared of another .
Hello .
Jana , meet me right now .
Vicky !
Hi .
Hello .
Sorry , I was too engrossed in listening to music .
What do you listen to ?
English .
Wow !
- Akon . - Who ?
Akon .
♪ " Wanna be my Chammak Challo . " ♪
The guy 's like Kumar Sanu of his country .
I see .
- You don 't know ? - No .
You missed the veneration again .
I guess I don 't get along with God too well .
Right . Right .
I ...
I brought this offering for you .
I 'm fasting today .
Even offerings are not allowed .
I see .
Doesn 't matter .
Whether you eat it or me , it 's the same .
By the way , we can go inside .
I know the priest .
I can arrange for a special veneration for you .
And even make a donation of 11 rupees in your name .
- Your name ... - Did you get the items on the list ?
Yes .
I got everything you asked for .
You didn 't tell me which brand of brandy , so I got every brand .
But it 's better this way . You can try every brand , for variety .
And , I couldn 't find a cat with completely white hair .
She had mixed colors .
But what will you do with all these things ?
Are you going to ask everything right now ?
Let 's go someplace else .
- At this hour ? - Yes .
Okay .
But where ?
Let 's go . I know a spot .
♪ " Fair ... you 're so fair . " ♪
♪ " Like the moonlight that 's ♪ ♪ falling on earth . " ♪
♪ " Bad ... very bad . " ♪
♪ " The world 's intentions are very bad . " ♪
♪ " I hope no one casts ♪ ♪ an evil eye on you ... " ♪
♪ " ... this thought keeps ♪ ♪ scaring me all day . " ♪
♪ " This silky dress ... that ♪ ♪ you 've worn tonight . " ♪
♪ " When you smile ... all ♪ ♪ my sorrows get alleviated . " ♪
♪ " I hope no one casts ♪ ♪ an evil eye on you ... " ♪
♪ " ... this thought keeps ♪ ♪ scaring me all day . " ♪
- Vicky 's gone tonight . - Where ?
Focus on my meaning .
I pondered over this a lot .
And the verdict I 've reached is pretty dangerous .
What is your verdict ?
You were a genius at school , then how are you so slow in real life ?
I go to the depth of every matter and weigh it properly .
My dear Pacific Ocean .
Why aren 't your depths showing you what I can see ?
This girl ...
And always during the festival .
And do you know who else shows up during the festival ?
Who ?
Stree !
Mister , open your mind
Has anyone else seen her except for Vicky ?
No .
And what does she ask him to get in her first love letter ?
- Cat hair , lizard leg ... - Tail .
It 's one and the same .
Who asks to get stuff like this ?
He 's not picking up .
- Mister , turn off your phone . - You shut your mouth .
And fill fuel worth 50 rupees .
50 again .
Why don 't you ever put more ?
Why don 't you try telling my father that ?
You try calling him .
He 's gone to meet her , I am telling you .
Our friend is in trouble , understand .
Stree has laid a trap .
And our love hungry friend , is heading straight for it .
He is actually cutting the calls .
Why do people become blind in love ?
How would I know ?
You can be anyone you want , but not a devotee .
Where do you think the new couple would have gone to spend some time alone ?
The lake .
SECOND NIGHT
How do you know about this place ?
And why did we come here ?
Because it 's dark out here . And no one comes here .
Dark .
He isn 't here either .
Where could he be ?
I am telling you , we 'll only find his clothes today .
Your clothes are very nice .
Where did you buy them ?
I designed them myself .
People call me the Manish Malhotra of Chanderi .
Isn 't it too tight ?
It 's just my body ...
How do you open it ?
- Listen . - Yeah ...
- Shall we leave ? - Why ?
- Are you scared too ? - No .
I am not scared of any ghosts or spirits .
But how long are we going to waste our time on a selfish guy ?
But he 's our friend .
Bittu .
Wait .
So what else do you stitch at your shop ?
Just skirts and long dresses , or anything else ?
Actually , we make everything .
Completely ladies fashion .
Skirts , tops , traditional dresses , tunics . Midis , minis .
Short dresses , long dresses , kaftans , fringe , party dresses .
Mirror work , stonework , designer panty , nightfall .
Nighty fall .
That 's it .
When will you give me my dress ?
It completely slipped off my mind .
- I troubled you a lot , didn 't I ? - Of course not .
It was no trouble at all .
And anything for you .
I should have taken your measurements that day .
I thought you did .
Normally I am good at this , but in your case , I goofed up .
So take it now .
But I don 't have my measuring tape .
Can 't you take my measurement without it ?
I can , but ...
Should I ?
Take it .
Okay , I will .
Hello .
Where are you ?
- Bittu . - Yes .
I am missing my mom .
Shall we go back ?
You 're right .
- Parents are more important than friends . - You 're right .
Let 's go back .
What happened ?
Let me check .
What ?
I think we 're out of petrol .
I told you , didn 't I ?
Tell me one thing ... is your father a menial labor ?
You own a big shop in the city .
From Manish Malhotra to Manish Behl .
What is this ?
Whether you fill 50 rupees petrol at a time or fill your tank .
It 's still the same .
The petrol pump is close-by . Push .
It 's your bike , isn 't it ?
You push .
Why should I ?
I 've been pushing it since we were kids .
What 's wrong with you ?
That Stree is wandering around the city .
And we 're stuck in the middle of nowhere .
And you want to know what 's wrong ?
Mom clearly said that I should come back soon .
If I don 't hurry up , she will lock the doors and sleep .
What now ?
Push !
Mummy !
Hello .
Where are you ?
Madam .
Where are you going ?
I knew it , selfish rascal .
What 's wrong with you today ?
I am your friend , not your slave .
First I go over to your house so that you can tuck yourself neatly under the blanket .
- And then I go home all alone . - But we do that all the time .
Not today .
Fine , let it be .
I 've been listening to your nonsense for a long time .
Go on .
Fine , you don 't have to .
Get going .
Weird guy .
- I hope Stree abducts you . - Same to you .
Son !
No ... no ...
If you ever come across the Stree , this is what you do .
Jana
No .
Don 't turn around .
Keep walking .
Jana
No ... No ... No !
Jana . My Jana .
Curse that Stree .
My Jana never even touched any female .
And now she must be sitting on top on him .
I told him a thousand times not to hang around with these worthless friends .
Jana could 've had a good job .
But these rascal friends spoiled him .
Lord , give him strength .
Give my son strength .
I know you went to meet her .
Stop getting jealous of my love life . Think about Jana .
Did anything weird happen ?
Weird how ?
Anything at all , when you were with her ?
What did you two do ?
Why ?
Just tell me .
We went to the temple .
Then to the river banks .
We were just sitting and chatting , and then she disappeared .
And didn 't return .
I knew it .
I knew it , Vicky .
What ?
- That your girlfriend is a ghost . - What do you mean ghost ?
Jana and I were coming to save you .
- And she took Jana instead . - What nonsense .
Snap out of your dream world , Romeo .
Why does your girlfriend show up only during the festival , and then disappear ?
She asks you to get ingredients for black magic in her love letter .
Have you ever seen her feet ?
Are they straight or crooked ?
Did you ask her name ?
Do you know her phone number ?
Has anyone seen her except for you ? Because I haven 't .
But ...
OH F * * K
I just don 't understand one thing .
How does she enter the temple ?
Are these ghosts atheists ?
Aren 't they scared ?
She never enters the temple , always stays out .
She doesn 't take the offerings either .
Vicky , for the first time I am feeling sad for you .
Because of all the things in the world ... you fell in love with a witch .
Go and ask her , your Stree , where she took Jana .
I miss him .
One more thing .
Don 't tell her that Bittu told you all this .
Otherwise , she might abduct me too .
Warning ! Warning ! Warning !
An important piece of warning for all the males in the city .
Stree is out hunting and the males are in threat .
The method to save yourself from Stree is written in this paper .
Remember it .
- Show me . - No , it 's not for you .
You 're safe .
If you ever run into Stree
then there 's just one way to escape
Under no circumstance will you ...
Hello !
How do you know so much about the Stree ?
I know everything .
Tripple BA , Double MA , literarian , musician , teacher .
I have all these degrees .
I spent my childhood amongst crocodiles .
Rudra Book Depot .
But why do we write " O Stree Come tomorrow " ?
We can write something else .
Like , " Stree , never come back again " .
As long as it 's working , let it continue .
And by the way , if we ever have an unwanted guest
we don 't directly say " Get lost and don 't come back " to him .
We politely say " Come back tomorrow " .
I 've heard that the Stree first s * * * * her prey before killing him .
That 's the system with female scorpions too .
She swallows the male scorpion which she mates with .
Listen wise guy , please don 't share your knowledge with us .
Leave all that aside .
Tell us what 's the solution to it .
My wife says that I should wear a saree when I step out .
Please don 't spread such rumors .
Or soon we 'll see everyone in our city draped in a saree .
" My beloved 's arrived " type .
No , no .
How does she know everyone 's name ?
Because all our databases are linked to her .
I see .
Shut up , idiot .
You see , two youngsters have already been abducted .
Be alert .
Poor guy was abducted from the town square . He was such a healthy boy
Wasn 't he your friend too , Vicky ?
But not anymore . Not anymore .
- Keep the glass down . - What ?
Trying to be over smart . Huh !
Get lost .
He 's still alive . My friend isn 't dead .
Brother .
Sir . Sir .
See for yourself .
Brother Vicky , you are amazing .
You stitched this dress in 31 minutes .
Sir .
- What happened ? - No ... it 's nothing .
No , I haven 't done anything . I didn 't do anything .
Don 't kill me , Stree . Don 't kill me .
What happened ?
Vicky , what 's wrong ?
It 's nothing .
You look like you saw a ghost .
Ghost .
No ... no ghost .
It 's nothing .
- You okay right , Vicky ? - Yes , I am okay .
I am all right .
- Is it ready ? - Yes , it is .
Thank you .
It 's all right .
Shall we go out somewhere ?
Out ?
I 'll take you to another one of my favorite spots .
No !
This is my favorite place .
- Let 's sit here . - Okay .
( Hanuman Chalisa )
There 's magic in your fingers .
And even in my feet .
I can turn it around like this .
Can you turn your feet around too ?
- Is there a problem ? - No . What problem ?
There is no problem .
Can I ask you a question for my personal knowledge ?
Do you believe in ghosts and spirits ?
I 've heard that a woman wanders in this city at night .
Called Stree .
She is a witch .
She abducts males .
Strips them .
I know she must have a good reason .
No one is born as a witch . Right .
I understand .
My friend Jana , he 's disappeared as well .
He 's a very nice guy .
People say that Stree took him .
Have you seen Jana ?
Can I ask you a question ?
Its personal , but don 't take it personally .
Are you ...
I mean not intentionally .
Are you ... Stree .
I just asked .
I don 't have a problem .
I was just confirming .
If you 're a ghost ...
I mean you are what you are .
If it 's anything like that , please tell me now .
I 'll just be prepared mentally . That 's all .
Uncle .
Do you see that girl standing there ?
What girl ?
That one ...
That ...
( Song Other languages )
You should listen to your friends as well .
But how can a beautiful woman like her be Stree ?
Was she beautiful ?
Sorry .
Think about Jana .
What condition will he be in ?
Lying somewhere naked in this cold .
What now ?
We 'll have to find someone who 's an expert in such absurd folklores .
You came to the right place .
I know everything .
- Doesn 't get me high . - Then why do you drink ?
In Shama 's memory , that 's why .
Leave Shama aside .
And tell us what you know about Stree .
I am doing research on Madam Stree .
And like they say , the fruits of hard work is always sweet .
Yeah ...
- And I got one too . - Sweet fruit .
No . Book .
Book .
Just a minute . Just a minute .
Here you go .
Ohh ...
KS .
Ka Su ...
- Are you researching on this ? - Not that .
This one . This is it .
This is Chanderi Puran .
Chanderi has its own manuscript .
Our city is older than you think .
The spot where you 're sitting .
If we dig beneath it , you 'll find the Harappa Civilization .
Right here .
Harappa .
You don 't say . Exactly under this spot .
So look , Chanderi Puran written by Shankar Shashtri .
Here we go .
Many years ago .
Many years ago there used to be a beautiful and attractive courtesan .
Every male in the city would dream about her .
Finally , she found a man who loved soul and not her body .
True love .
And talk about your generation .
Love at first sight .
Then your place or mine .
What direction is this generation heading in ?
Brother Rudra .
Don 't try to be a dad .
- Please read ahead . - Yes .
They both decided to get married .
But the other males couldn 't tolerate their joy .
And before their wedding night , some jealous people murdered both of them .
Since then she has been wandering in this city .
Looking for her love , and complete her wedding night .
And this can only happen when she will find her lost love again .
Such insolent people .
They can 't tolerate someone 's happiness .
Every female has the right to find her true love .
Brother Rudra . Brother Rudra .
We can have this debate later .
First , tell us if there 's a method to stop Stree ?
There I just one way to get rid of Stree ...
- Yeah - Turn the page .
- Turn the page . - Okay .
The city 's main business was silk .
People had such high Scarcity for education ,
... that they actually believed that the moon was their uncle .
The main ...
How come Shastri turn up in west from east .
After page 66 there is page 80 .
Where are the rest of the pages ?
This is why I don 't let anyone in .
Children tear pages from the book and make paper boats .
How will we save Jana now ?
Just a minute .
I 've seen this place .
- You have ? - Yes .
Where ?
Above the hill .
- We should go there . - Then let 's go .
- We might find something here . - Yes .
- Go . Go on you two . - What " go " ?
- You must come along too . - Me ?
- Brother Rudra , you have done research . - Of course .
I see ...
Wait a minute then .
Let me take a sip . Take this along .
Shama , I am going .
THIRD NIGHT - We 'll run out of petrol .
How much further , Vicky ?
Just a little further .
Stop !
Stop .
What ?
I am allergic ... to dust .
Come on .
It 's so dark around here .
- What if she abducts me ? - She is a female , not a male .
She doesn 't use force against your will , like men .
She will first ask for your permission .
Hello Mr. Tom-Dick-or-Harry .
And if you turn around .
Then she will think it 's a yes .
Yes , means yes .
Then she will take you away .
So under no circumstance will you turn around .
- No turning around . - No .
Let 's go .
Jana .
What are you doing ?
Brother Rudra . Give me the alcohol .
Alcohol .
Why ?
This is no time or a drink .
No .
Power .
No power .
Okay , give me .
Save some for me .
You 're worried about the alcohol .
You go that way .
Brother Rudra , you search upstairs .
- Why ? - And I will look here .
Let 's stay together .
We don 't have time for that .
Hail Goddess ! Hail Goddess !
Mom always said to learn the Hanuman Chalisa .
Now see .
Sorry , mom .
Snake ! Snake ! Snake ! Snake !
Run .
Snake !
Mummy !
Brother Rudra ! Brother Rudra !
Where are you going ?
I was just warming up .
- I saw her . - You did .
Brother Rudra !
Jana .
Vicky ...
Stree ... it 's me . Vicky .
Remember I stitched your dress .
I am here for Jana , he 's a ... very nice guy .
In fact , he calls you sister-in-law .
Vicky ...
I stitched your dress in 35 minutes , Stree , and you want to abduct me .
You hurt me .
I won 't turn around .
- Vicky ... - I can 't hear you at all .
Hello . Hello . Hello .
Daddy .
Vicky !
Are you okay ?
- Are you okay ? - Yes , I am fine .
Is she gone ?
Don 't know .
Don 't know ?
But at least one good thing happened .
You 're not Stree .
You know , like in the morning ...
Sorry .
Shall we go back ?
- But Vicky is still inside . - Bittu .
Where were you ?
Did you see Jana ?
No !
Run brother Rudra . He 's fallen prey as well .
That 's not her .
- She is not Stree . - You are lying .
That 's the girl .
The letter ... Remember .
The dress .
" Vicky Please ! "
That 's her .
I swear she risked her own life to save mine .
You two would 've ...
Been amazed .
She flung her dagger at the witch .
If we had posted her video on Youtube , it would 've been an instant hit .
# daggergirl .
But what is she doing here ? How does she know we 're here ?
Your friend is not the only one missing .
Many people go missing every year .
I 've been coming here for the past three years during the festival .
So that I can get rid of her for good .
I know he will never come back .
But still ...
You can share your sorrow with me .
It will lighten your burden .
No !
Okay .
By the way , where did you learn this art ?
I had to wander around for it .
I went to ascetics , and tantric .
Tantra , magic , hypnosis , and spells from the red book .
I learned everything .
I 've had only one mission for the past three years .
Defeating Stree .
I tried everything I knew .
But it wasn 't enough .
I thought I was ready .
I thought that I would defeat her this time .
You see , ma 'am . I 've done extensive research on this subject .
Research .
I have books on magic spells , hypnosis , and other art forms in my library .
You can come over if you need any help .
Even we have a shop for lady 's fashion .
Best in town .
If you need anything at any time , just let me know .
And anyway ... it 's always better than stitched clothes .
I don 't like readymade .
Shall we ?
Vicky .
What happened ?
Jana . My Jana is back .
My son is back .
My son , where were you ?
- Where were you ... - You 'll tear his ( the ) clothes .
He 's lost so much weight .
Forgive me , son . Forgive me .
You really are his friend .
- I said such bad things . - It 's all right .
It 's okay , aunty .
Jana , it 's your mom , your mom .
I want to go sleep .
He wants to sleep .
- Yes son , let 's go . - Come on .
Please send my coat back .
Okay , aunty .
Bye , Jana .
Aunty . Aunty .
She took my husband .
She took my son too .
She took him too .
She took my husband .
My husband too .
But ... how did so many people disappear ?
Someone erased the ink .
Jana , look what Stree did .
She abducted a dozen men .
And she 's also erased the ink .
Jana .
You ...
Why are you sitting like that , Jana ?
And your palms ...
Jana .
I am your mother . Listen to your mom , son .
Jana , spare your friends at least .
Listen to me , I am already 70 % damaged .
Jana .
We 're humans , not kites .
Vicky , look at Jana 's hand . He erased the ink .
- Divert his attention ? - Me ?
Go .
Jana .
Someone get a blanket .
Jana , stop .
Jana . Jana . Jana . Jana . Jana .
It 's Vicky .
Jana .
Quiet !
Or else I will slap you .
Jana .
What are you doing ?
It 's Vicky .
Bittu ! Bittu !
Come on .
This is the only solution left .
Wear saree and bangles like women do .
Your solutions were not effective at all .
That Stree took 20 men .
Yes , Vicky .
Yes , I know . I am coming .
I am coming .
We want our youngsters back .
Whoever brings the missing men back ,
... will be rewarded 10,000 for every male .
Understand ?
This city wants freedom .
Freedom .
Everyone knows ...
Stree is a thief .
Let 's all unite .
And drive Stree away .
You give us men ...
We 'll give you freedom .
It 's the smoke coming on my face .
- Bittu , untie me . - Wait .
No one listens to him .
David has turned into Goliath today .
How can someone beat up your own friend ?
We cannot waste any more time .
Jana is completely under her control .
We must do something solid before the festival ends .
You 're experienced in this field , suggest something .
If we can find out more about Stree , then I can come up with something .
But from where ?
- We found a book at his shop . - Library .
We found a book in his library .
But the pages were missing .
What if we find the guy who wrote that book
then he would know what was written on those pages .
- Do you know that guy ? - I know everything .
Is he alive ?
He lives in Emergency .
- What ? - ICU !
Emergency .
Which book are you talking about ?
Respected Mr. Shastri .
You wrote the history of our city in a book .
Chanderi Puran , remember ?
The book was launched in my Rudra Book Depot .
You used to sell adult books back then .
Mr. Shashtri , that Stree abducted our friend .
She abducted many more males too .
Can we get them back ?
Stree .
Please , Mr. Shashtri .
We request .
Did the emergency end ?
We 've been banging our heads against a wall .
This man doesn 't remember anything .
Yes , Emergency is over .
No-no-no .
Mr. Shashtri , we 're talking about Stree .
Stree . - Stree .
Like " Stree Come back tomorrow " .
Stree .
What is a Stree ( Female ) ?
She has no s tature compared to males .
What ?
She should always stay within her limits .
Never step out of the home .
Her job is to keep her husband happy , and bear children .
And if she crosses her limit , then burn her alive at the cross .
He has no solution .
Such vile thoughts .
We just wasted our time with him .
What kind of a writer is he ?
Is this what he writes ?
What about Jana now ?
He 's too strong to control .
Let 's think .
He 's got such a filthy mind .
It 's not me , its this city that has a filthy mind .
They used that Stree as long as they wanted .
And then got rid of her .
And that man who gave her respect , they took him away as well .
They will all die .
Everyone .
As long as there 's even one male in this city , she won 't stay quiet .
Just one ... one man can douse this fire .
- Who is he ? - How does he look ?
Wheatish color , long nose . And treats himself like a king .
Born in the arms of the oak tree .
The prince of his family .
Love reflects in his eyes .
A true artist .
He 's the true protector of this city .
A prostitute 's son who 's a bachelor .
Courtesan 's son who 's a bachelor .
A courtesan 's son who 's a bachelor .
Wheatish color , long nose . And treats himself like a king .
Born in the arms of the oak tree . The prince of his family .
Vicky . Weren 't you born at your grandma 's house ?
And there was an oak tree behind her house .
Yes .
So ?
And you 're the only son .
Prince .
Very good .
Wheatish color , long nose . And treats himself like a king .
- He has wheatish color . - And a long nose .
And , you always think of yourself as a king .
Love reflects in his eyes .
And a true artist .
There 's love in your eyes .
And Stree saw that , which is why she didn 't abduct him .
There 's love in my eyes ?
Stree can see it , not her .
And you 're an artist as well .
Aren 't you getting carried away now ?
What artist ?
Vicky is the best ladies tailor in the neighboring three districts .
Exactly .
This is a good coincidence .
But we must find someone who has all five qualities ?
And what about the fifth quality ? courtesan 's son ?
How will find him ?
Courtesan means that right ?
That ...
No one told him .
Nobody .
Everyone knows , but you don 't know .
What ?
- What ? - Look ...
There 's no need to feel bad .
Some mothers are school teachers , some are government officers .
Some make pickles .
- Your mother was that ... - What ?
That .
What ?
Courtesan !
I will kill you right now .
I thought you never meant it when you called me a bas * * *
You ...
This is absurd .
And in front of her .
Vicky. it 's true .
Jana , I will break your head .
Vicky .
Don 't look at me .
I won 't believe you .
My mother was not a courtesan .
- Listen ! - No .
Vicky !
We 've found the protector of the city .
He will deal with Stree .
- You mean Stree . - Yes . Stree .
One more .
Brother Vicky , mom 's asking when you will return her blouse .
Dad .
What were you lecturing me about energy ?
You 've done a lot of friendship when you were young .
Tell me something .
Did you do friendship with mom , or marry her ?
Blouse petticoat .
Who was she ?
Why didn 't you tell me ?
You kept lying to me .
Daddy , I won 't drink again . Swear on mom .
Swear on my dad , okay .
Sorry .
Eat .
You could 've told me this once .
That 's all .
Eat .
I talked to daddy .
And I thought how does it matter .
She was my mother after all .
Maybe my father 's someone else too .
But I know only one father .
The guy who stands at the shop with the measuring tape .
And who thinks that my talent is the greatest talent in the world .
But this city ...
Everyone knew about me , but they never made fun of me .
Otherwise , people like to gossip .
I always knew that I wasn 't meant for altering dresses .
But I didn 't know that I was born to save these people .
Lord chose a really unique mission for me .
" Born in the arms of the oak tree . "
" The sole prince ... "
" The son of a courtesan who 's a bachelor . "
If I really am the son of a coutesan
then I will save this city .
Along with Jana , I will save everyone !
Bittu gather everyone .
What do we know about the Stree ?
- She is scary . - Ferocious .
No ! She can read .
Have you ever heard about a ghost or spirit who can read ?
Right .
Meaning we 're up against an educated witch .
She is the new generation witch .
Point no . 2 .
She comes every year during the festival , to abduct men .
But if you write outside your house " O Stree , come back tomorrow " .
Then she reads it and thinks ...
" Oh ... okay . Rest today , and I 'll come back tomorrow . "
Meaning she listens .
Meaning she is obedient .
No. 3 .
She is very stupid .
Next night she comes back again .
Reads the same line again and thinks ...
" Oh shit , now I 'll have to come back tomorrow again . "
" This is cheating . "
And she goes back to her home .
Poor thing doesn 't understand that these people are s ...
I mean making a fool of her .
- She has a low IQ level . - Exactly .
And we 're much smarter than her .
Thank you .
And , if we get serious
then we can easily get rid of this witch forever .
- Then let 's get serious . - Correct . Let 's get serious .
But what are we going to do ?
Wedding night .
But brother Rudra , aren 't you too old for that ?
No me .
No !
According to Mr. Shashtri 's book ,
Stree wants her wedding night which was left incomplete .
Yes so .
And if you 're the protector of this city
then you must fulfill her wish .
What are you saying ?
Have you lost your mind ?
- No . - What are you saying ?
My father never even let me watch a wedding night on TV ,
... how can I do it with a witch ?
Yes .
I am the protector , shouldn 't I prepare for a battle or something .
The battle begins after the wedding night .
Brother Rudra ...
You mean , me and that witch ...
We just have to use it as bait .
We must lead her to you , that 's all .
Remember she saw love in your eyes .
Yes .
- And then ? - Then leave it to me .
She is very strong in her own home .
But I know how to overpower her when she is out of her house .
But where will we call her ?
Right here , in Vicky 's Palace .
Best place .
Show the bait .
Hurry up .
Stree is out hunting today .
Don 't step out of the house and lock the door .
Okay .
Come back soon .
I feel scared alone . - I 'll be back soon .
Keep the doors closed .
Vicky , you 're looking really handsome .
- Now wear this cap . - No , no .
- I said wear it . - No , no , caps . You 'll ruin my hair .
- But the groom has to wear ... - I don 't want to ...
Wear it .
Dad had such vivid dreams about my wedding .
Who knew that I 'll be marrying a witch some day .
Don 't worry .
You 're getting a chance to save the entire city .
Not everyone gets this opportunity .
Don 't be scared .
Don 't you want to save Jana ?
Don 't you want to make him a human being again ?
What is the plan ?
What do we do ?
Stree will definitely come here after reading the message on the wall .
When she looks into your eyes , don 't look away .
Instead look into her eyes .
I know a spell .
That spell will render her powerless .
And then we must drive this dagger through her heart .
Dagger ? How can I ...
We 're waiting inside .
Don 't be scared .
Let 's go .
Listen ...
Will your spell work ?
90 %
What is 90 % ?
Maybe 99 % .
Meaning there is a 1 % chance I 'll be dead .
Daddy ...
Let 's go .
Listen .
I am going ...
Don 't worry , okay .
Don 't forget you are Vicky .
The guy who can spend a night with a witch .
In case I don 't come back , don 't come looking for me .
And ... look after my dad .
O Stree come back tomorrow .
O Stree there are no men here .
O STREE COME HERE .
I think it 's her .
She isn 't coming inside .
Is she suspicious ?
Stree is smarter than you all thought she is .
- Jana . - Jana .
Jana .
Listen to me .
Leave him .
Jana .
Vicky .
- Jana ! - Jana .
Vicky is missing .
Vicky .
Vicky isn 't here .
He 's not .
Where could he be ?
Meaning Stree was here and she took her lover .
Don 't say that .
All our arrangements , the wedding night preparations , didn 't work .
Where did your sister take him ?
- Vicky just sent a message , on WhatsApp . - What ?
He just shared his location .
Stree .
Where are you , Stree ?
Stree , I ...
Okay . Fine . I am sitting here .
I 'm not going anywhere .
I am sitting right here .
This is the same place .
I guess she took him to the bedroom .
And she won 't let him go until she spends her wedding night with him .
Oh , God .
Stree ... I am ready .
Come on this bed . We 'll spend our wedding night .
I am getting ready . I am getting ready .
I 'm taking it off .
Do I have to take my pants off too ?
Fine , I 'll take it off .
I am ready now . Come on .
Sorry . Sorry . Sorry . Sorry .
Sorry , Stree . I understand that you 've no interest in all this .
I respect you .
I 'll even wear my clothes back .
See , I am wearing them back .
Don 't kill me , Stree .
I am the only son .
Vicky !
Jana .
What happened ?
Is she dead ?
She is just powerless at the moment .
But we must finish her before she gets her powers back .
Where are your clothes ?
Sorry , I ...
I thought in order to save the city , I will have to sleep with her .
But you know what , I don 't think she wants any of it .
Here you go .
You must pierce her heart with this dagger .
And cut off her braid .
Braid ?
How did her braid get in all this ?
And , how will I do this ?
You do it , please .
I would 've done it if I could .
You will have to do it .
You 're the protector of the city . Come on .
Yes , I know I am the protector , but I am a tailor , not a killer .
Kill her before she wakes up again .
Take it .
- Come on . - Yes .
Go .
Do we have to kill her ?
Poor thing is lying down so comfortably .
This is exactly how the people of this city treated her .
And we 're doing the same .
So what 's the difference between us and them ?
She must have a reason .
She is trying to find her true love .
Let her go , please .
There must be another way .
Like lizard 's tail , cockroach soup .
Then cut off her braid .
This will make her powerless .
And , she won 't die either .
Okay .
- No , no , no . - Look into her eyes .
Find the dagger .
Look . Look .
Vicky , open your eyes .
She won 't do anything if you look in her eyes .
It 's not working .
She is hungry for love .
For love ...
Look into her eyes with love .
Love .
More love , Vicky .
I am shitting in my pants , and you want more feelings .
Quiet !
What is all this yelling for ?
This is no way to take revenge .
I am the protector of the city , so show some respect .
Always screaming .
Vicky .
Here .
Throw the braid away .
Are you okay ?
Yes .
Dagger .
Sit up .
Get up .
Sit up straight .
- I think she 's gone . - Yes .
Isn 't it ?
She kept attacking her .
But I snuck up behind her and cut off her braid .
Then she disappeared .
And didn 't come back .
But is the Stree dead or not ?
Tell me .
Meaning she will come back again next year .
- She 's only hungry for one thing . - No. it 's two .
What ?
Love and respect , which this city never gave her .
And that was this city 's biggest mistake .
And we were going to repeat the same mistake .
And if this city gives her the respect , which she never received .
Then she might leave us alone .
These brave men together have protected the city
and we will never forget their contribution .
All the youngsters who went missing in the last two days have returned .
Are you listening ?
- There she is . - Stop . Stop .
Sister-in-law .
The flower . The flower .
- Good luck . - Thank you .
Everyone was looking for you .
You wore the dress .
Does it fit well ?
You took my measurements so well .
This is for you .
I could 've never fought against the Stree without you .
Thank you .
You are very nice , Vicky .
I wish we had met before , then we could 've become friends before .
Will you be my friend ?
You mean friends , or ...
Yes . Isn 't that what friendship means ?
No .
There 's another meaning for friendship in our town .
What if I want to talk to you , or meet you ?
I don 't even have your number .
Just think of me .
Do you have to go ?
Please wait for a few more days .
Please .
Vicky , please !
Name ?
You didn 't tell me your name ...
This is my first time where he 's smitten by love but doesn 't know her name .
Maybe this is true love .
' For the past three years , I had only one motive . '
' Defeating Stree . '
' I tried everything I knew , but it wasn 't enough . '
' There 's always a method to control any power . '
' Just cut off her braid . '
' She will become powerless , and won 't die . '
' I would 've done it long ago if I could . '
' You 're the protector of the city , you have to do it . '
ONE YEAR LATER .
O STREE PROTECT US .
♪ " Music . " ♪
♪ " Everyone 's talking about you . " ♪
♪ " They all know that you 're an angel . " ♪
♪ " You 're hard to get ... " ♪
♪ " ... your poor beloved 's been waiting . " ♪
♪ " All I know is there 's a cave ... " ♪
♪ " ... but the cave 's hard to open . " ♪
♪ " No matter what I do , ♪ ♪ but you 're never impressed ... " ♪
♪ " ... your beloved 's ♪ ♪ been wandering around . " ♪
♪ " I 've played all the shots right . " ♪
♪ " And seen have all slots . " ♪
♪ " But I haven 't hit ♪ ♪ the jackpot yet , but ... " ♪
♪ " You 'll get it ... You 'll get it . " ♪
♪ " You 'll get it ... " ♪
♪ " I 'll get it too . " ♪
♪ " The miracle 's going to happen . " ♪
♪ " You 'll get it ... You 'll get it . " ♪
♪ " You 'll get it ... " ♪
♪ " Someday we 'll all get it . " ♪
♪ " Be patient my friend . " ♪
♪ " I warned you before ... " ♪
♪ " She will come draped in a saree ... " ♪
♪ " Draped in a saree ... " ♪
♪ " And come for your ... " ♪
♪ " Heart ... Your heart ... Your heart ... " ♪
♪ " She comes alone . " ♪
♪ " When she comes along . " ♪
♪ " Just meet me . " ♪
♪ " Meet me in my dreams . " ♪
♪ " Meet me completely decked up . " ♪
♪ " Because ... " ♪
♪ " You 'll get it ... You 'll get it . " ♪
♪ " You 'll get it ... " ♪
♪ " I 'll get it too . " ♪
♪ " The miracle 's going to happen . " ♪
♪ " You 'll get it ... You 'll get it . " ♪
♪ " You 'll get it ... " ♪
♪ " Someday we 'll all get it . " ♪
♪ " Be patient my friend . " ♪